web-blinds.com 2010-06-11

# web-blinds.com - privacy policy

We are fully committed to protecting your privacy. This statement describes our policy: 

## What information do we collect and how do we use it?: 

The principle activity of web-blinds.com is the supply of window blinds. In order to do this, we need to collect information from you when you place an order, request free samples, or when you save quotes, window measurements or rooms from 'room creator', but we will only retain this information with your permission. We always ask for your email address as this information is essential for processing any orders you place with us and it also helps us tailor our service and provide you with a more personalised shopping experience. All other information, such as your name, address and telephone number is optional for all processes apart from placing an order. If you do decide to register with us you can view the personal information we have collected about you by visiting the 'my web-blinds.com' page of the site. 

Any personal information collected by us is controlled by us at,

web-blinds.com  
Unit 2 Churchill Park  
Private Road No 2  
Colwick Business Park  
Nottingham  
NG4 2JR

We may also use the information we collect about you to notify you of any news on our goods and services that we think you may find valuable. At every point on the site where this information is collected, we will give you the option to tell us if you do not want your personal information used in this way. If at any stage you decide you would prefer not to receive such information, please contact us at the above address or email us at [enquiries@web-blinds.com.](mailto:enquiries@web-blinds.com)

## How do we protect your information?

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. 

Please see our security policy for further information.

Any web-blinds.com employees who have access to your personal data are obliged to respect your confidentiality and take this responsibility very seriously.

## Will we share the information?

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These functions include delivering packages, sending emails, analysing data, processing credit card payments and providing marketing assistance. The companies have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

web-blinds.com is part of the Hillarys Group of companies. Other companies within the Group may also wish to provide you with news and information about goods and services that may be of interest to you. At every point on the site where this information is collected, we will give you the option to tell us if you do not want your personal information disclosed in this way. If at any later stage you do not want to continue receiving such information, contact us at the web-blinds.com address (see above) or email us at [enquiries@web-blinds.com](mailto:enquiries@web-blinds.com)

We may share statistical data about visitors to this site and sales patterns with Group Companies or other parties. We will not sell or share any of your personal information unless you agree to us doing so.

## What are Cookies?

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by our web server to your web browser. It enables our server to collect information back from your browser and is used to identify you when you visit our website. Cookies allow us to track visitors to web-blinds.com, so we can determine the most popular areas of the site and make it more user-friendly. Our cookies do not contain any personal information but they do enable us to store your details in the 'my web-blinds.com' section of the site between your visits. 

You do not have to accept cookies and it is possible to set up your browser to notify you when you receive one. This will give you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. Please refer to the help section on your browser toolbar or the information that came with your browser software.

## What about Links?

Our site may contain links to other sites, which we believe may be of interest to you. These sites are not owned or controlled by us and we are not responsible for their content. They will also have their own privacy and security policies, which we suggest you read. 

## Policy changes

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page of our site and will be effective immediately. This policy was last updated on 19 June 2009. 

## How do I contact web-blinds.com?

If you are unsure about any aspect of our privacy policy, or if you have a complaint or any other comment to make on our website, please contact us at: 

web-blinds.com  
Unit 2 Churchill Park  
Private Road No. 2  
Colwick Business Park  
Nottingham  
NG4 2JR  
Email:[enquiries@web-blinds.com](mailto:enquiries@web-blinds.com)  
Tel:0845 604 9611
